(function(){const r=document.createElement("link").relList;if(r&&r.supports&&r.supports("modulepreload"))return;for(const t of document.querySelectorAll('link[rel="modulepreload"]'))l(t);new MutationObserver(t=>{for(const s of t)if(s.type==="childList")for(const f of s.addedNodes)f.tagName==="LINK"&&f.rel==="modulepreload"&&l(f)}).observe(document,{childList:!0,subtree:!0});function n(t){const s={};return t.integrity&&(s.integrity=t.integrity),t.referrerPolicy&&(s.referrerPolicy=t.referrerPolicy),t.crossOrigin==="use-credentials"?s.credentials="include":t.crossOrigin==="anonymous"?s.credentials="omit":s.credentials="same-origin",s}function l(t){if(t.ep)return;t.ep=!0;const s=n(t);fetch(t.href,s)}})();const w=[{question:"Which team isn't in the current F1 season?",answer:[{answer:"McLaren",correct:!1},{answer:"Aston Marten",correct:!1},{answer:"Force India",correct:!0},{answer:"Haas",correct:!1}]},{question:"Which team won the first Formula 1 World Constructors' Championship?",answer:[{answer:"Ferrari",correct:!0},{answer:"Mercedes",correct:!1},{answer:"McLaren",correct:!1},{answer:"Red Bull Racing",correct:!1}]},{question:"Which manufacture has confirmed to be the engine provider for Red Bull ready for use in 2026 season?",answer:[{answer:"Renault",correct:!1},{answer:"Audi",correct:!1},{answer:"BMW",correct:!1},{answer:"Ford",correct:!0}]},{question:"The movie RUSH is based on which to former F1 drivers? (you should watch it if you haven't!)",answer:[{answer:"Lewis Hamilton & George Rustle",correct:!1},{answer:"Kimi Räikkönen & Sebastian Vettel",correct:!1},{answer:"Niki Lauda & James Hunt",correct:!0},{answer:"Ayrton Senna & Alain Prost",correct:!1}]},{question:"In what year did Formula 1 switch to using hybrid power units rather than naturally aspirated engines? (S/O STOP OIL)",answer:[{answer:"2010",correct:!1},{answer:"2012",correct:!1},{answer:"2014",correct:!0},{answer:"2016",correct:!1}]},{question:"Where is the Prince George Circuit located?",answer:[{answer:"France",correct:!1},{answer:"United States",correct:!1},{answer:"United Kingdom",correct:!1},{answer:"South Africa",correct:!0}]},{question:"When was Roman Grosjean involved in a fire quenching crash?",answer:[{answer:"2020",correct:!0},{answer:"2019",correct:!1},{answer:"2021",correct:!1},{answer:"2018",correct:!1}]},{question:"When did the principal of Williams, Claire Williams retire?",answer:[{answer:"2015",correct:!1},{answer:"2018",correct:!1},{answer:"2020",correct:!0},{answer:"2012",correct:!1}]},{question:"What is the average speed around Spa for a F1 car?",answer:[{answer:"210kph",correct:!1},{answer:"212kph",correct:!1},{answer:"248kph",correct:!1},{answer:"230kph",correct:!0}]},{question:"Who's was the youngest F1 race winner at just 18 years and 228 days old?",answer:[{answer:"Lewis Hamilton",correct:!1},{answer:"Sebastian Vettel",correct:!1},{answer:"Aryton Senna",correct:!1},{answer:"Max Verstappen",correct:!0}]},{question:"Which Formula 1 circuit is known for having the most corners in a single lap?",answer:[{answer:"Circuit de Monaco",correct:!0},{answer:"Suzuka Circuit",correct:!1},{answer:"Circuit of the Americas",correct:!1},{answer:"Spa-Francorchamps",correct:!1}]},{question:"In which year did Ayrton Senna achieve his first Formula 1 World Championship?",answer:[{answer:"1986",correct:!1},{answer:"1988",correct:!0},{answer:"1990",correct:!1},{answer:"1992",correct:!1}]},{question:"Which team holds the record for the most consecutive Constructors' Championships in Formula 1?",answer:[{answer:"Ferrari",correct:!1},{answer:"Mercedes",correct:!0},{answer:"McLaren",correct:!1},{answer:"Williams",correct:!1}]},{question:"At which circuit did Michael Schumacher secure his record-breaking 7th Formula 1 World Championship title?",answer:[{answer:"Suzuka Circuit",correct:!1},{answer:"Circuit de Monaco",correct:!1},{answer:"Nürburgring",correct:!0},{answer:"Interlagos",correct:!1}]},{question:"Which country has produced the most Formula 1 World Champions?",answer:[{answer:"Germany",correct:!1},{answer:"United Kingdom",correct:!0},{answer:"Brazil",correct:!1},{answer:"Italy",correct:!1}]},{question:"Which driver holds the record for the most pole positions in Formula 1 as of 2021?",answer:[{answer:"Lewis Hamilton",correct:!0},{answer:"Ayrton Senna",correct:!1},{answer:"Michael Schumacher",correct:!1},{answer:"Sebastian Vettel",correct:!1}]},{question:"Which Grand Prix is known for its unique twilight start-to-night finish race format?",answer:[{answer:"Bahrain Grand Prix",correct:!1},{answer:"Singapore Grand Prix",correct:!0},{answer:"Abu Dhabi Grand Prix",correct:!1},{answer:"Australian Grand Prix",correct:!1}]},{question:"Who is the youngest Formula 1 World Champion in history?",answer:[{answer:"Sebastian Vettel",correct:!0},{answer:"Lewis Hamilton",correct:!1},{answer:"Fernando Alonso",correct:!1},{answer:"Max Verstappen",correct:!1}]},{question:"Which team introduced the *double diffuser* innovation that sparked controversy in the 2009 Formula 1 season?",answer:[{answer:"Ferrari",correct:!1},{answer:"Red Bull Racing",correct:!1},{answer:"Williams",correct:!1},{answer:"Brawn GP",correct:!0}]}],m=document.querySelector(".game-menu__start-button"),i=document.querySelector(".container__next-question"),u=document.querySelector(".container__questions"),o=document.querySelectorAll(".container__answer"),h=document.querySelector(".game-menu__score"),p=document.querySelector(".game-menu__restart");if(!m||!i||!u||!o||!h||!p)throw new Error("Issues with the selectors...");let a=0,c=20;const d=e=>{const r=w[e];u.innerHTML=r.question,console.log(d),o.forEach((n,l)=>{const t=r.answer[l];n.textContent=`${l+1}. ${t.answer}`,n.classList.remove("correct","incorrect")})};o.forEach(e=>{e.addEventListener("click",()=>{const r=w[a].answer[Array.from(o).indexOf(e)];console.log(r),r.correct?(c--,h.textContent=`Score - P:${c}`,e.classList.add("correct"),e.classList.remove("incorrect")):(e.classList.add("incorrect"),e.classList.remove("correct"))})});const y=()=>{a++,a<w.length?d(a):S()},g=e=>{for(let r=e.length-1;r>0;r--){const n=Math.floor(Math.random()*(r+1));[e[r],e[n]]=[e[n],e[r]]}};g(w);const q=()=>{a=0,c=20,d(a),h.textContent=`Score - P:${c}`,i.style.display="flex",o.forEach(e=>{e.style.display="flex"})},S=()=>{const e=document.createElement("h1");e.innerHTML=`Thank you for playing the F1 quiz! It was a tough race but we finished the day at P${c} we'll try again next week.`,e.classList.add("thankyou-message"),u.innerHTML="",u.appendChild(e),o.forEach(r=>r.style.display="none"),i.style.display="none"};i.style.display="none";m.addEventListener("click",()=>{d(a),o.forEach(e=>e.style.display="block"),h.textContent=`Score - P:${c}`,m.style.display="none",i.style.display="flex"});i.addEventListener("click",()=>{y()});p.addEventListener("click",()=>{q()});
